wysk.com 2014-06-27

# Wysk | Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

All pages copyright ©2012-14 Wysk®. All rights reserved.

Wysk provides business registration, information exchange, communication, and credit evaluation services to businesses across the United States through our Wysk Website and related services. All capitalized terms in this Privacy Policy are defined in our Data License Terms and Conditions. This privacy policy describes how We collect, use, manage, and protect user information; please read it carefully. By using the Wysk Site You consent to our collection, use, management and protection of your information as described in this notice.

**1\. What information does Wysk collect?**

When You register for and use any Wysk Services, Wysk collects and saves the information that You enter. We also collect information from business owners and principals, from businesses’ creditors, vendors and suppliers, and from public records such as business registrations, Uniform Commercial Code filings and bankruptcy filings. The business information that We collect may include the following:

  * Business registration data, which may include addresses, officer information, status, key dates, and other information submitted to the business registrar;
  * Filings related to a business, including UCC filings, bankruptcies, lawsuits, judgments, liens, trademarks, and real estate records;
  * Company and business professional contact information, including name, title, address, phone number, fax number and e-mail address;
  * Detailed company profiles and statistics, including number of employees;
  * Background information regarding company management, such as the educational and career histories of company principals;
  * Company operational histories, including territories, subsidiaries, affiliates and lines of business;
  * Detailed trade and business credit information, including payment histories and patterns;
  * Summary business information regarding profitability, debts, assets, net worth and business relationships;
  * Business professional data as it relates to their professional lives, such as name, company, title, business contact information and trade associations; and
  * Credit/debit card information in order to process certain customer payments.

Entering this information is optional, but entering certain information is required to use some aspects of the Wysk Services. We also collect information about Website visitors indirectly through standard Web logs, such as IP addresses, browser types (e.g. Internet Explorer), areas of the Website that are visited and the Website from which a visitor came. We routinely use this Web log information in the aggregate in order to administer and improve our Website. While some of this data may be traceable to an individual, We only seek to identify individuals whom We believe are using our Website for improper purposes.

If You make a purchase or sign up for a trial subscription on the Wysk Site, Wysk will collect your credit or debit card information and use it solely for the purpose of processing payments for your purchases of Wysk Services.

**2\. Security**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about You to those employees who need to know that information to provide our products and services to You. Wysk maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your nonpublic personal information.

When ordering online, Wysk does not cache, or save, your information if You skip to another page before You submit your completed order. When You submit information it is protected when it is sent over the Internet. Wysk employs a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connection that provides an encrypted connection between your computer and Wysk. Personal or secure information is encrypted during transmission and is stored on a secure Wysk Server. Credit card numbers are encrypted when transmitted and remain encrypted when stored.

**3\. Wysk Logs And Cookies**

Wysk log information is automatically gathered every time You visit our Wysk site by the computer that hosts our Wysk site (called a "Wysk Server"). The Wysk Server automatically recognizes non-personal information, such as the date and time You visited our site, the pages You visited, the Wysk site You came from, the type of browser You are using (e.g. Internet Explorer), and the type of operating system You are using (e.g. Windows 2000).

Each time You log on to “Customer Dashboard”, our server software sets a unique session ID known as a “cookie.” A cookie contains the ID of the backend session that You are interacting with each time You make a new connection to the Wysk Server. It is passed back to the server for your subsequent activity, user ID, and criteria set information The cookies are intended to save You time by allowing You to return to pages previously viewed. They are temporary and will be automatically deleted at the end of each session.

**4\. Can You request that public data  related to you or your business be removed from the Wysk Site?**

The business data, including officer information, that Wysk displays is provided by official sources of public records. If you believe there is an error in the data, or you are concerned about your personal information being made public, you should contact the source of that data (the Secretary of State in your business's home state, for example) and ask about their procedures for removing or changing your public business records. Once your information is updated at the source, it will automatically be updated on Wysk.com as part of our regular update process.

If you believe that your public business data is subject to a law or regulation that allows you to opt out of having that information displayed on Wysk.com, please mail an opt-out request to the address below. In your request, state which information you would like removed, and which federal, state, or local law or regulation requires its removal.

Wysk Opt-Out  
2401 Main Street, Suite 100  
Houston, TX 77002

Please allow a reasonable amount of time for Wysk to review your request and, if appropriate, remove the information from our site.

**5\. What control do You have over your personal data?**

You can review and edit the personal information You have entered in your personal profile at any time by visiting your Customer Dashboard.

You should keep your username and password confidential at all times to help safeguard your personal information. Do not let others log in using your username and password.

**6\. How does Wysk communicate with You?**

Wysk will send emails to the address You provide when You sign up for an account in order to provide certain components of the Wysk Services. Events that will trigger an email to You include:

  * The creation of your user account
  * The initiation of a new subscription or free trial
  * Changes in the status of a subscription, such as expiration, cancellation, or reactivation
  * Billing activity on your account

These emails are necessary to the proper functioning of the Wysk Services and cannot be turned off.

From time to time, Wysk will also send You information about Wysk products, services, events, or discounts that Wysk think You may be interested in. By signing up for a user account with Wysk, You agree to receive these occasional promotional emails. You can opt out of Wysk promotional emails at any time.

**7\. What else should You know about Wysk’s Privacy Policy?**

Wysk reserves the right to change this policy at any time, with or without notice. The revised Privacy Policy will become effectively immediately upon posting. You can view the most current version of the Privacy Policy at [www.wysk.com](http://www.wysk.com/).

The Wysk Site contains links to other Wysk sites and other Websites. Wysk has no control over and is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of third party sites.

The Wysk Site and Wysk Services are not intended for children under 18 years of age. If You are under 18 please get a parent or guardian’s permission before using this site or submitting any information to Wysk.

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us [support@wysk.com](mailto:support@wysk.com)

Updated May 1, 2014

All pages copyright ©2012-14 Wysk. All rights reserved.
